https://letstalkcounseling.com/privacy

Are You A Provider or A Client? ×
ProviderClient
Your Privacy Matters
Notice of Privacy Practices
LetsTalkCounseling.com is required to comply with health care privacy laws and regulations. We go to great lengths to ensure that your personal information is secure. Your privacy is very important to us. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with the following principles to ensure the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
The Company DOES NOT disclose personal information to third parties, except where required by law. This includes selling, renting, trading, sharing, or giving information via any medium.
Non-Identifiable Data: When you interact with LetsTalkCounseling.com through the Site, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. This information is collected passively using various technologies and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. LetsTalkCounseling.com may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by LetsTalkCounseling.com affiliates, agents or service providers. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.
The Company collects non-identifiable data during account creation and use of the Site. This information may be used as follows:
for verification of the user’s legal right to use the software,
to identify accounts when support is requested by account holder,
to inform users of product changes,
for support and marketing,
to enforce licensing terms,
for inclusion in aggregate usage data for the purpose of studying and improving the product, and
to enable features of LetsTalkCounseling.com
The Company does not use personally identifiable information for any use other than stated above. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We may change this statement from time to time with notice.
Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve our Users and Providers, LetsTalkCounseling.com often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and LetsTalkCounseling.com may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. LetsTalkCounseling.com may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
Information Provided to Providers: We do not collect any information that a User provides directly to any Provider and not through our Site, including but not limited to during a session with such Provider. The Provider, along with any applicable professional guidelines, determines the recording, storage and use of any information that is collected in a session, and is solely responsible for maintaining the privacy of such information. If a user has questions about the privacy of information they share with a Provider, they should discuss directly with the Wellness Professional.
Let's Talk Counseling
2911 Sharon Rd
28211
Charlotte, NC
Tel: (844) 880-8255,
E-mail: hello@letstalkcounseling.com
© 2001-2020 Let's Talk Interactive, Inc. DBA Let's Talk Counseling. If you are in crisis, call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline, a free, 24-hour hotline, at 1.800.273.8255. If your issue is an emergency, call 911 or go to your nearest emergency room.
Let's Talk Counseling
does not offer crisis counseling or emergency services.
